All four of you are going to hell.
Nii-san's the only one that
stands a chance anymore!
Kageyama-kun, use all of your powers!
I can't let them all die.
I have no choice but to
fight with all I've got.
Don't do it, Mob.
When things go south,
it's okay to run away!
Damn it! I can't believe this is happening.
R-Reigen-san just...
I have a bad feeling about this...
A tremendous amount of stress
is going to hit Nii-san.
Something's going to happen!
If everyone is not special
Maybe you can be what you want to be
We'll be able to find our answers
1%, 2%, 3%, 4%, 5%, 6%, 7%, 8%, 9%, 10%...
11%, 12%, 13%, 14%, 15%,
16%, 17%, 18%, 19%, 20%...
21%, 22%, 23%, 24%, 25%...
Admiration, troubles, pump up
26%, 27%, 28%, 29%, 30%...
Searching for yourself, telepathy
31%, 32%, 33%, 34%, 35%...
Asking for the impossible, psycho punch
36%, 37%, 38%, 39%, 40%...
Youthful Salt Splash
Mob? Mob? What do you want?
Mob? Mob? Why do you want?
Mob? Mob? Who do you want?
Move! Move! Just like Mob!
If everyone is not special
Maybe you can be what you want to be
Even if you hold onto happiness and sadness
Your life is your own, OK?
It's OK you are not special
We'll all be able to find our answers
81%, 82%, 83%, 84%, 85%,
86%, 87%, 88%, 89%, 90%...
91%, 92%, 93%, 94%, 95%,
96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
"Mob Psycho 100" 91%, 92%, 93%,
94%, 95%, 96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
91%, 92%, 93%, 94%, 95%,
96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
Honestly...
Honestly, I don't want to hurt anyone.
But if I don't, we're going to be killed.
That's the feeling I got.
I realized that I have to do it
in order to protect everyone.
That's the kind of situation
we're in right now.
Nii-san...
And yet... Master told me...
""Run Away""
"'Don't Fight'"
...that it was okay to run away.
So...
"'Leave it to Master'"
I-impossible...
Don't scare me like that!
I thought you actually cut me for a sec.
How are you standing, Reigen-san?
So that katana was a fake after all.
It totally felt plastic.
So what kind of trick did you use
to cut the floor earlier?
Hey, what's going on?
He's acting like he usually does.
Then... I'll just chop off your head next!
Ow!
Listen... Real adults don't have time
to play with toy swords!
That's Kageyama-kun's master
for you, I guess.
Sakurai, move!
Candy-chan!
Whoa! An evil spirit?
Hey, Mob! Do something.
Huh? That was surprisingly light.
--A plushie?
--Huh?
What are you, some mascot?!
Oh, sorry! I didn't mean
to rip your costume!
What? Is Reigen-san actually the real deal?
Don't get cocky.
Crap! He's surrounded!
Huh? What is this?
Is this like the newest form
of 3D imagery or something?
What were you even trying to do?
He nullified all of them?
Is this man some kind of monster?
How can this be?
Are you telling me someone this skilled
still exists in this world?
He must be eliminated.
We can't have him getting in the way
of our world domination.
Huh? I see. You were using
some kind of magic trick, too, huh?
You bunch of frauds.
Just try that thing with
the black orbs again.
--That many?
--Is he going to be okay?
Leave this to the adult here.
My body seems to be in great shape today.
Master really is amazing.
"It's okay to run away."
As soon as he heard those words,
the explosive amount of energy
building up within Mob
changed its direction.
There are times when the power
of one's words is unfathomable.
Those with power must fight.
That responsibility had made
Mob's bridge collapse.
Sometimes, however...
One's heart can find a resolution
just by being offered a helping hand.
As a result, all of Mob's energy was
temporarily tossed over to Reigen.
In essence, he had successfully run away
and was feeling rather refreshed now.
All that was left in his heart
was gratitude toward his master.
"Reigen Arataka"
n Mobil
Are these soap bubbles?
My Black Orbs swallow up and
destroy anything they touch...
And this man is touching them
with his bare hands...
Why? What happened to the man that was
trying to run away just a moment ago?
Looks like I'll have to put
my body on the line, too.
Five Hundred Kilogram Tackle!
One Ton Punch!
Two Ton Guillotine!
Hey, you still conscious?
No matter how powerful an esper you are,
I can't call you an excellent esper.
Because you have no desire for domination.
The reason you're so powerful
and yet so unknown
is because you're living while
hiding your powers, right?
But I am different!
I am filled with ambition,
and I want to go higher and higher,
--and hold this world in-- --Get off me.
Stop talking while you're still on top of me.
What a dense energy barrier!
I see. The reason my Black Orbs
burst earlier was because
the energy they were trying to
take in was way over their limit!
Inconceivable... Who are yo--
Also, when you're speaking to someone,
take off your mask!
Hup!
Oh, it came off.
Actually, what's with this strength?
Could it be him...?
That's the only plausible explanation.
Seriously, someone your age
needs to quit messing around.
Wh... What could you possibly know?!
To hell with society!
Don't try and lecture me when
you've only seen its good side!
As soon as I was born,
I was abandoned by my parents.
I was all alone.
One happy family? Mother's cooking?
I got to experience none of that as a boy.
I was terribly bullied at an orphanage,
and I cursed the world!
"Curse" I was terribly bullied at an
orphanage, and I cursed the world!
"Curse"
If I hadn't, I wouldn't have survived!
And then I awakened to my powers...
I was able to survive
because of these powers!
Anyone who rejects my way of living can--
What? What's with that look?
Don't look at me like that!
I totally understand how you feel.
H-He's the same as me?
When I was in grade school,
maybe it was around fourth grade...
I forgot to tell my parents that it
was sports day at school that day,
so I was the only one with nothing to eat.
That's actually your fault...
What are you even talking about?
A story about when I felt lonely as a boy.
Don't compare that stupid story to mine!
Jugan Air Gun!
It's the ultimate weapon of destruction.
Die!
If all else fails, I'll put you to sleep
with this cursed cologne!
Hm? I don't really get it,
but don't point that at others.
I'll take that.
Are you still doing that crap?
You use the psychic powers you've been
blessed with for the stupidest things.
--What?
--You're like a little kid with a knife.
I can't bear to watch.
Who do you think you are?!
What's that thing on your forehead?
Th-That's...
It has nothing to do with you.
Then what's with these things
that look like shoulder pads?
Those are to guard my shoulders...
Which means they're just accessories
and have no purpose, right?
Huh?
Don't get the wrong idea.
No matter what kind of special powers
they may be blessed with,
people are still only human.
Nothing more, and nothing less.
You guys haven't realized that yet!
You're so addicted to your special powers,
you've developed tunnel vision.
You're plotting world domination when
you haven't even seen the world?
Don't make me laugh!
No one's going to follow you like that!
First, get rid of those childish
shoulder pads and grow up!
You, too! You just want
to escape from society, right?
If you want to make it big,
you have to live in reality!
That's where you start.
You're telling us to return
to being commoners?
What? No way! Don't look at this lightly!
You still don't get it, do you?!
Who the hell do you think you are?!
You're nothing more than a commoner!
You're just a part of the masses!
B-But Claw is a noble--
I'm a commoner!
I'm much more powerful than you,
and I'm still just a commoner...
So what does that make you?!
He dragged them out of their delusions
and back into reality by force...
By shattering their dreams...
Your master's amazing!
Yeah.
No! That is absolutely not true!
The division leader's face...
He's that old?
I thought that maybe he was a girl, but...
I reject your claims!
"People are only human.
Nothing more, and nothing less."
--That is what you said, isn't it?
--Yeah.
That is incorrect. That's far too cruel.
We are special!
We are superior lifeforms
to the rest of humanity!
I'm sure you have to
believe that to even go on.
But sadly, society has no interest in you.
Society this, society that!
No group made according to your
stupid yardstick is big enough for me!
Quit relying on those around you, old man.
You're making me sad here.
I was born with these powers,
so what's wrong with me showing them off?
What's wrong with changing the world?!
You stupid ape!
To me, you're all no different from monkeys!
It's hard to live!
Even though I'm so special!
I'm so amazing, so why won't you
just acknowledge that?
The world should put me on
a pedestal and worship me!
That is the only world that is worthy!
No, having psychic powers doesn't
make you popular at all.
And that's all there is to it.
You'll never be popular. Give it up.
I'm going to erase you all...
Erase this whole building and start over!
Crap. Looks like I'm out of gas.
Mob. Lend me your powers again.
Actually, I'm also...
Crap! We're being sucked in!
Disappear! Disappear! Disappear!
You just don't know when to give up.
--That's--
--Damn it!
You can also...
Disappear!
A mass of gravity, huh? Interesting.
Imagine the gravity going backward...
It's not an actual black hole.
If it's made from psychic powers,
I can always find a way to deal with it.
Old man...
You're no longer needed.
And as for you...
I'm disappointed in you.
You coward.
The Seventh Division will be dissolved.
I was to inspect the place and take
anyone who seemed useful back to HQ...
What are you talking about?
Weren't you a trainee?
Sadly, there wasn't anyone worth my time.
At least on the inside.
Well, see ya.
The evil spirits have been
whittled down to one...
The poison jar has been completed!
Matsuo, there's nothing left for us to do.
Come out, my ultimate evil spirit,
Marshmallow-chan!
--The hell's that?
--Dimple!
I was finally able to get out.
All right! Now that I've
regained some of my strength,
I can help out a hundredfold!
--It's already done.
--Huh?
You mean the climax happened without me?
--Is this an evil spirit?
--Whoa!
Why are you able to see me
when I'm not in my visible mode?
--They're strong.
--No, we were weak.
I've come to a realization.
Those guys just might be able to stop it...
Stop Claw from world domination...
"Mob Psycho 100"
Really? Let me see.
--Here, look.
--Oh, that's great!
Let's go together!
Ah, Tsubomi-chan...
She's as cute as ever today.
--Our eyes met!
--You're staring way too much.
--Mezato-san!
--You're panicking too much.
Staring at girls is all well and good,
but today's the day that you're
going to talk to me, Mob-kun.
No, I've got club again today.
I'll wait until you're done.
But I've got my job after that.
Jeez. When are you going
to tell me everything?
Your older brother came by last night.
Huh? My brother?
You must've been through a lot, too.
We both went a little crazy.
I'm about to go apologize to
Onigawara-kun and the others.
I'll go with you.
But are you sure?
The entire student body's going to hate you.
That's my own fault for
doing something so stupid.
And... now my brother is on my side,
so I'll keep in line.
Wha--? So it was you guys
who planted the recorders on me.
That was a crappy thing to do.
And I knew anyway,
so it's not like it matters now.
--Huh?
--What do you mean?
People didn't care whether
I was actually the culprit or not.
They were chomping at the bit for a stick
to beat me with, a chance to kick me out.
That's where the problem was.
I realized that I was hated
by everyone around me,
and how weak my heart was.
Hey.
Your brother was worried about you.
He thought I was going to kick your ass
since I was so pissed off,
but I'll let things slide since you are
the shadow leader's younger brother.
What's wrong, Onigawara?
You out of energy?
The hell do you think you're talking to?!
I'm still going to grow,
just like White T Poison.
Body Transformation!
Fight on! Fight on! Fight on!
That's your older brother.
Is he okay? He looks like
he's about to pass out.
Yes. Despite how he looks,
to me, Nii-san is stronger than anyone else.
But he's passed out on the ground.
By the way, President, did you
give up on finding telepaths?
Huh? Actually, I haven't even started yet.
Right now, it's like a wild-goose chase,
so I'm trying to get some actual leads.
You guys should at least try to help me out.
I tried searching on the Internet
but couldn't find any.
Of course you're not going
to find them that easily!
--Hey.
--Musashi-san!
What the heck, Mob-kun?
You passed out again?
Inukawa, get some water!
Oh, sure.
What's up, old man?
Why'd you bring us here again?
I guess you haven't given up
on psychic powers.
Actually, I wasn't the one
who brought you here today.
It was at the behest of someone else.
Hello, nice to meet you.
So you guys must be the
research subjects here.
Oh, it's another hot guy.
I see. Your powers are still weak,
but it'll definitely be worth nurturing them.
He's Hanazawa-kun, one of the guys
who fought that organization that day.
What do you think? Do you guys
want to get stronger with me?
--Huh?
--Since one of their divisions was crushed,
I'm sure Claw will make a move soon.
It'll be for self-defense and so you
can fight back when that happens.
Leave the support to me.
Kageyama took all the glory that night.
Yeah.
Let's do this!
Yeah!
So, what brings you here?
I'm only here because
Shigeo asked me to come.
He passed out from anemia and
can't help with exorcising spirits.
Actually, do you even need Shigeo anymore?
You awakened to psychic powers, didn't you?
Don't be stupid.
Those were all Mob's powers.
The only thing I gained from it
is the ability to see you now.
Otherwise, nothing's changed.
So you're just a plain ol' con artist again.
You're a rather rude spirit.
All right. Then you help me out.
Dimple, was it?
Huh? Why do I have to help you?
That's why he had you come over, isn't it?
If he was just calling out,
a phone call would have sufficed.
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
S-Seriously? Who do you guys think I am?
What? Aren't you Mob's errand boy?
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
I'm a high-level evil spirit!
I'm disappointed in you.
You coward.
Did I do something lame?
Did I make some kind of mistake?
Ugh, again? I told you to
fix that habit of yours.
Shigeo's just at that age.
Let him bend all the spoons he wants.
You always say that.
Here, Nii-san. Let me see it.
What's with these kids?
Here, Nii-san.
Thanks, Ritsu.
Well, whatever.
Oh, there it is.
Hello? Oh, I'd dropped my phone.
Huh? The Seventh Division?
They were crushed.
Espers from outside infiltrated the place
and slaughtered the upper echelon.
The division leader, Ishiguro-san,
was no big deal either.
As for all of the underlings,
the enemy totally won them over.
Sho, what are you talking about?
I'm asking you for a status report
on the inspection.
The organization you're so proud of
isn't the best in the world at all.
Quit messing around and come back
to Japan already, you stupid father.
Making me do an annoying
inspection like that...
At least I got that off my chest.
Yes... Very soon.
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
And now the news.
"Multiple Tsuchinoko Sightings Continue"
"Multiple Tsuchinoko Sightings Continue" We've received numerous
reports of tsuchinoko sightings throughout Seasoning City.
"Multiple Tsuchinoko Sightings Continue"
"Multiple Tsuchinoko Sightings Continue" City Hall, in a bid
to reinvigorate the area, has put a bounty on the tsuchinoko
City Hall, in a bid to reinvigorate the area,
has put a bounty on the tsuchinoko
and is requesting help in capturing it.
Hello? Are you free right now?
Meet me in 90 minutes,
and wear clothes you can exercise in
and don't mind getting dirty.
"Mob and Reigen" "- A Giant Tsuchinoko Appears~" and wear
clothes you can exercise in and don't mind getting dirty.
"Mob and Reigen"
"~A Giant Tsuchinoko Appears~"
--We're going to capture a tsuchinoko.
--Huh?
Doesn't that excite you?
Isn't this private property?
This is the kind of place
where those suckers show up.
Have you ever seen a tsuchinoko, Master?
Nope. It's just a hunch.
That's pretty random.
Don't you have any passion
when it comes to UMAs?
Bigfoot, Nessie, and tsuchinoko!
I hear there's a bounty on its head.
Well, there's that, too.
--Master, um...
--What?
I don't think amateurs are supposed to
go this deep into the mountains.
Mob, we might be amateurs
when it comes to hiking,
but you have psychic powers.
Add to that my ingenuity...
Oh! Over there!
Look over there, Mob!
I knew this place was the jackpot!
Huh? Was there actually a tsuchinoko?
Look! Matsutake! It's huge!
Oh... After all that talk about passion,
he's already distracted by the matsutake.
What the hell is that?!
Whatever it is, apparently it's starving!
We're going to exorcise it, Mob!
Actually, Master, isn't that the UMA?
You idiot! Those things don't exist!
--Kill it!
--Okay...
That's amazing. It shrank so much
after you exorcised it.
Er, actually, it just threw up a lot.
What the hell was that thing to begin with?
You already picked that many?
Well, whatever. Let's go home.
Huh? What about the tsuchinoko?
What are you talking about?
Those things don't exist.
I'm gonna grill up some
matsutake at the office.
--You'll have some, right?
--Yes.
Guess we should buy some kabosuy, too.
Yes.
"Hakata Salt"